manulife ifunds a quick guide
how can i increase my regular savings
plan amount
log in to manulife ifunds and click on
the menu button in the top right hand
corner
click on regular savings plan here you
can view and select your existing
rsps click on the view or
update contributions button for the rsp
that you would like to make changes
the current details of the selected rsp
are
summarized here click change
rsp this screen shows the active
contributions tab
which lists all funds that you are
currently contributing
in your rrsp to top up the monthly
contribution for an existing fund
click on that fund to expand it and
select the edit button
key in the new amount that you would
like to contribute monthly mark the
check box
and click save and continue your updated
total monthly contribution for all funds
under this rsp must be within your
maximum monthly contribution
if the limit is exceeded there will be
an over
limit mark clicking next will lead you
to this roadblock click close and adjust
contributions to return to the previous
screen
and adjust accordingly please ensure
that you have read the offering
documents
and fully understood its contents before
checking the box
review the changes that will be made for
your rsp
read and acknowledge the important notes
terms
disclaimers notice and declaration
click next input the one-time passcode
that will be sent to your registered
mobile number
and click confirm you and your advisor
will receive an email notification
with an additional sms sent to you
it's that easy to learn more reach out
to your manulife investment management
advisor
or contact our customer service at zero
three
two seven one double nine two seven
[Music]
one
you